Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Records Documenting Golf
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, records documenting golf
1925-1988
RU 937
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4
The records consist of topical files, correspondence, reports and scrapbooks documenting golf at Yale.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-B (YRG 38-B), Records documenting specific sports at Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Department of Athletics, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Existence and Location of Copies
Golf scrapbooks are available on microfilm (560 frames on 1 reel, 35mm.) from Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library, at cost. Order no. HM184.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of topical files, correspondence, reports and scrapbooks documenting golf at Yale.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College sports; Golf; Scrapbooks; Yale University -- Golf; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
- Scrapbooks of the golf team, 1932-1942; Accession 2006-A-035
  Scope and Contents
  Arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Scrapbooks
    - 1932-1938 (Box 1, Reel 1U)
    - 1939-1942 (Box 2, Reel 1U)
- Records of the golf team, 1925-1988; Accession 2006-A-109
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
  Arranged by topic.
  - History, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Golf Associations [Yale Golf Club, New England Golf Association, U.S. Golf Association, and Yale Golf Association], 1925-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Yale Athletic Association [Binder: Hints to Managers], 1927 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1937-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4 - 5)
  - Team reports, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Golf committee, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Men's Golf -General, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Women's Golf -General, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence [Donations], 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Publications, 1960-1996 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)